疑云笼罩在这届政府班子上
A cloud of suspicion hangs over this administration.
有过掩饰吗？ 谎言？
Were there cover-ups? Lies?
哦 天 我恨弹劾
Oh, God. I hate impeachments.
太90年代范儿了
They're so '90s.
哦 总统现在被参议院
Well, the president now has the Senate
和众议院紧追不舍 祸不单行
and the House after him. Gonna rain pain.
总统的下一步行动是什么？
So what's POTUS's next move, Jonah?
哦 我的嘴巴都封住了
Oh, these lips are on lockdown.
哦 你不知道啊
Right. You don't know.
不 我只是有个"不问不说"的原则
No, I just have a "don't ask don't tell" policy
对我知道的事情
about the things that I know.
或者我不知道的事情
Or that I don't know.
Jonah 不要说话 别呆在这
Jonah, don't talk, don't stay.
你需要滚回你的西部世界 (西翼双关)
You need to fuck off and go back to Westworld.
但是 女士 你得滚了
- But, ma'am-- - You need to fuck off.
但是 女士 我说了滚
- But, ma'am-- - I said fuck off.
三次滚了 你出局了 是的 女士
- Three fucks, you're out. - Yes, ma'am.
哦 呃 伙计们 大家都请到我办公室来
Yeah. Uh, guys, everybody in my office, please.
呃 Gary 你为什么不过来坐到我身边？
Um, Gary, why don't you come sit here next to me?
好的
Okay.
我已经跟Amy说过这个了
I've already told Amy this,
但我有些事需要告诉你们所有人
but I have something that I need to tell you all.
我想我知道你要说什么
I think I know what you're gonna say.
我已经决定不和总统联合参与
I've decided I'm not going to join POTUS
下一次竞选了 我要离开
in the next election. I'm gonna get out.
哦
Yeah.
女士 向您致以我最深切 最深切的同情
Ma'am, you have my deepest, deepest sympathies.
好吧 呃 我还没死
Okay, well, I'm not dead.
我的计划是
My plan is
两年后我会离开
that I'm gonna leave in two years,
但我会竞选总统
but then I'm gonna run for president
在那四年后
four years after that.
但与此同时 很明显我无法留住每个人
But in the meantime, I obviously can't keep everybody on.
不 没什么
No, it's okay.
所以如果你们需要寻找其他工作
So if you need to look for other jobs,
那么你们得开始思考了
then you need to be thinking about that.
现在没人在想那个 女士
No one's thinking about that right now, ma'am.
我们从未想过这件事
Furthest thing from our minds.
我仍在消化这条消息
I'm still digesting the information.
不过...我很需要接这个电话
Although I should really take this call.
嗯？ 哦 哦 哦
- Yeah? - Yeah, yeah, yeah.
哦 你对此份工作的投入...
Well, your devotion to this job...
哦 唔 嗯 ... 很激励人 Dan
- Yeah. Mm-hmm. Yeah. - ...it's just inspiring, Dan.
他不是接电话 他是在打电话 对吧？
He's not getting a call. He's making a call, right?
你好 是的
Hi. Yes.
能请你转告Chung州长
Can you please tell Governor Chung
Dan Egan已经准备好和Chung聊一场了？
that Dan Egan is ready for the Chung chat?
你好 McKensie参议员 你好吗？
Hi, Senator McKensie. How are you?
你真的认为她会离开吗？
You really think she'll go?
天 那太遗憾了
God, that's such a shame.
不 那表示我完全没活干
No, it means I have absolutely nothing to do.
我刚才是为她遗憾
I meant for her.
一样 这大概表示
Still, this might mean
我们可以有更多的时间在一起
that we could spend more time together.
我们慢慢来
Let's take it one day at a time.
天哪
Sweet Jesus.
非常感谢您在这么短的时间内能接见我 Davison先生
Thank you so much for seeing me at such short notice, Mr. Davison.
我的荣幸 Wilson小姐
Happy to, Miss Wilson.
我是你效率和精确度的狂热崇拜者
I'm an ardent admirer of your efficiency and precision.
哦 好 那样的话 进入正题吧
Oh, well, in that case, let's get right to it.
很好 我尊重你的简洁
Excellent. I respect your brevity.
这都有点咄咄逼人了
It's almost threatening.
是的 Kosynski国会议员
Yes, Congressman Kosynski.
或者我该说Kosynski导师？
Or should I say mentor Kosynski?
是的 先生 呃 我一直将您视为导师
Yes, sir. Well, I always thought of you as a mentor.
我爸爸的父亲形象太怪异也太遥远了
The father figure my own dad was too weird and distant to be.
就像那晚你留宿 第二天早上我们一起看报纸的时候？
Like that night that you stayed over and we read the papers the next morning?
唔 那很不错
Uh-huh. - that Was really Nice.
我想 呃 那是
And I thought, yeah, that is something
我今后一辈子都可以做的事情
that I could do for the rest of my life.
哦 你知道 我喜欢睡觉和报纸
Yeah, well, you know, I like sleep and newspapers
和别的人一样 但 没错
- as much as the next person, but... - Right.
今后一辈子？
the rest of your life?
你知道 你会得褥疮
You know, you're gonna get bedsores.
把你安排到我的
I would have no problem finding you a position
统计梦小组里怎么样？
within my Dream Metric team. Sound good?
没问题 先生 我们达成一致了
- Yes, sir. - We are simpatico.
我们搞定了 很荣幸和您共事 先生
- We have a deal. - Pleasure doing business with you, sir.
是的 是的 Blackwell法官 您好吗？
Yes, yes. Justice Blackwell, how are you?
非常感谢您回电话给我
Thank you so much for calling me back.
你很快？ 哦 没错
- You fast? - Oh, yeah.
他们叫我华盛顿闪电 -
They call me the Washington Flash.
我很怀疑
I doubt that.
好吧 让我们赶紧跑一遍吧
All right, let's get this over with ASAP.
对这个傻大二逼来说可不容易
It's not gonna be easy with this big, gangly
他动起来就像是...
piss flap over here who moves like--
嘿 你动起来像什么 Will？
hey, what do you move like, Will?
我就像密西西比警察
I move as slowly as a Mississippi detective
侦查年轻黑人谋杀案一样慢 (种族歧视最臭名昭著的南方州之一)
investigating the murder of a young black man.
没错 准备好了吗 Mike？
That's right. Ready, Mike?
嗯 完 哦 您先请
Yeah, abso-- oh. Right behind you.
嘿 女士 您知道这个消息会
Hey, ma'am, you know you're gonna break
让总统心碎
the president's heart with this news.
我希望我可以敲断他的脊柱
Wish I could break his spine.
但我不能 因为它是用果冻做的 (没骨气)
But I can't, 'cause it's made of Jell-O.
别这样 您当副总统是美国有史以来最棒的事情
Come on, you being veep is the best thing that's ever happened to America.
Gary 这糟透了
Gary, it has been shit.
不 没有 就是的 我不干了
- No, it hasn't. - It has. I'm getting out.
哦 副总统女士 我之前告诉你什么了？
- Oh, Madam Vice President. - What did I tell you earlier?
又来？ 没错
Again? - Yeah.
抱歉 Ben 正要去见总统
Excuse me, Ben. Gonna go see the president.
呃 不 不 你不能 他取消了
Uh, no. No, you're not. He's canceled.
取而代之的 是跟我见面
And you're gonna meet with me instead.
女士 我之前正要跟您说这个
Ma'am, that is what I was going to tell you earlier today
直到您对我说... 滚开
until you told me to-- - Fuck off.
您是在接完我的话还是再对我说一次那个？
Are you finishing my sentence or are you telling me that again?
都是
Both.
是的 女士
Yes, ma'am.
好 走吧
Good. Go ahead.
国会议员...
Congressman...
喔 你很快
Wow, you're fast.
只是想知道您是否需要一个顶级的媒体人
Just wondering if you could use a top press guy.
哈! 我真的一点都不需要你 Mike
Ha! I really don't have any need for you, Mike.
你有些过时了
You're kind of obsolete.
你就像是困在过去的维京海盗
You're like a Viking stuck in time.
我有很强的人脉 真的?
I have excellent contacts. - Really?
很高层的人 先生 非常高
Very high up people, sir. Very high up.
或许你能给我联络上Charlize Theron (奥斯卡影后)
Maybe you can hook me up with Charlize Theron.
很好笑 但我是认真的 先生
Funny, but I'm being serious, sir.
不 我也是认真的 我想干她
No, I'm being serious, too. I'd like to fuck her.
不管怎样 你为什么要离开？ 你和你的老二都卡在副总统的无咖啡因咖啡里了？
Why'd you leave anyway? You get stuck with your dick in the veep's decaf?
不 我们只是都需要新的挑战
No, we just all need new challenges.
我们？ 什么 整个小组都要离开？
We? What, is the whole team leaving?
不 不 不 先生 去他妈的
- No, no. No, sir. - Holy shit.
她要退选了 不 完全不是
- She's leaving the ticket. - No, absolutely not.
我们他妈的有协议 我两年后当选参议员
We had a fucking deal. I make Senate in two years,
六年后我们一起参加大选
we run together as a team in six.
协议就是这样的 你他妈为什么不自杀 Will？
- That was the deal. - Why don't you fucking kill yourself, Will?
让我澄清一下 先生 如果她要退选的话
Let me be clear, sir. She may be planning to run in six years
那么她可能打算六年后参选
if she was leaving the ticket,
而我没有真的说她会
which I have not actually said she will.
哦 我滴苍天 谢谢你停下来
Oh, fucking God, thank you for stopping.
你知道吗？ 如果我之前还不知道
You know what? If I didn't already know
你工作做得有多烂 你刚刚也证明了这一点
how shitty you are at your job, you just proved it.
我有些重大的消息 女士
I have some very big news, ma'am.
哦 我有巨大的消息
Well, I have huge news.
事实上 我向你保证我的消息会是头版的那种
In fact, I guarantee you that my news is front-page news.
而你的大概是第六页(娱乐版)
Your news is probably more like a page six,
Kardashian的那种无聊消息 (娱乐家族卡戴珊)
Kardashian crap news.
总统知道这一切将如何结束
POTUS knows how this is all going to end,
所以他喝了我那一蓝色超大马克杯
so he drank the poisoned Kool-Aid
的毒Kool-Aid饮料
from my very big, blue mug.
哈？ 两年后他不会竞选连任了
- Huh? - He isn't going to run again in two years.
你认真的？
Are you serious?
不 我是他妈的Joan Rivers(著名喜剧演员)
No, I'm Joan fucking Rivers.
我当然是认真的
Of course I'm serious.
一旦党内领袖发现他不会参选
Once the party leadership figures out he's not gonna run,
那么所有弹劾狗屁都会烟消云散
then all the impeachment bullshit is just gonna fade away.
那么 呃
So, um--
那么为什么他不来对我说？ 为什么是你告诉我这个？
so why didn't he tell me this? Why are you telling me this?
因为他没法忍受那表情 像那个
Because he couldn't stomach the look-- like that,
就像那个 控制不住的喜悦
just like that-- of unbridled joy.
Ben 我在心底
Ben, I am crying
默默地哭泣
very quietly on the inside.
而在你的脑海里 你正在他的墓上跳舞旋转
While in your mind you're doing pirouettes on his grave.
哦 别告诉我你没有为此高兴
Oh, don't tell me you're not happy about this.
你终于能摆脱这里了
You're finally getting out of here.
哦 不是工作让人沮丧
Well, it's not the job that's depressing.
生活才让人沮丧
Life is depressing.
走吧
Let's go.
不 我可以 我能做到这个
No, I've got it. I can do this.
我没事
I'm fine.
耶!
Yes!
操!  天哪!
Fuck! Gosh!
Ahem.
你好 Sue
Hi, Sue.
因为一些紧急事件 我们想见副总统
We'd like to see the vice president as a matter of some urgency.
不行 操你的 我从偏门进
- No. - Fuck this, I'm going in the side door.
你那么做的话 特勤局特工可能会拧断你的脖子
You do and Secret Service might break your neck.
那就悲剧了 是么？  女士
- That would be a tragedy. - Yeah? Ma'am.
哦 你好 Roger 我们能谈谈吗？
- Oh, hi, Roger. - Can we talk?
我们当然能谈谈 嘿 能请你给我酸奶吗？
Of course we can talk. Hey, could I have my yogurt, please?
哦 这 别吃得太快
Oh, here. Don't eat it too fast.
哦 住嘴 大惊小怪的家伙
Oh, stop it, Nervous Nelly.
好了 给我来点流质的食品 加把勺子
All right, get me something sloppy with a spoon to eat.
你想来点酸奶吗？ 不 谢谢
- Do you want some yogurt? - No, thanks.
你看起来不错 顺便说 哦 谢谢
- You look good, by the way. - Oh, thanks.
什么 你在锻炼还是什么？
What, are you working out or what?
是的 我用老的焦虑疗法消耗卡路里
Yeah, I'm burning calories with the old anxiety diet.
哦 你知道的 焦虑(anxiet-ease精油)
- Oh. - You know, the anxiet.
如果你想做有氧运动 你得先有心才行啊
If you want to get some cardio exercise, you have to have a heart.
我听说了一个很糟糕的谣言
I heard a pretty lousy rumor
说你两年后不会再和总统一起竞选了
that you're not running for reelection with POTUS in two years.
那很令人困扰 因为我有点需要
Oh. - And that would be disturbing
你再次以副总统的身份参选
because I kind of need you to run as VP again.
然后我进入参议院
And then I get in the Senate
然后你和我一起参选
and then you and I run together as a team.
记住 这是协议 是的 我记得那个
- Remember, that was the deal. - Yeah, I remember that.
你从哪听来的谣言？
Where did you hear this rumor?
哦 从小姜饼那
Oh, I heard it from the Gingerhead Man.
有小胡子的裂缝(嘴) Mclintock(同名电影主角)
The gash with the stash. McLintock.
什么 你在开玩笑？
What, are you kidding me?
Mike视信息为敌 忘了它吧
Mike sees knowledge as the enemy. Forget about that.
那么你两年后会和总统一起竞选？
Then you are running with the president in two years?
两年后我绝对会参选
I am absolutely running in two years.
那之后的四年 竞选连任 宝贝
And then four years after that, reelection, baby.
你说竞选连任是什么意思？
What do you mean reelection?
不是竞选连任 那个时候是竞选
Not reelection. Election at that time.
是的 没错 你和我竞选
Yep. right. - you And I election.
等等 但你刚刚为什么说竞选连任？
Wait. But why did you say reelection?
什么? 你说了竞选连任
What? - you said reelection.
那就意味着有什么其他的事情发生了
Which implies that perhaps something else is going on.
我指的是参选 你知道我说的是什么
I meant election. You know what I meant.
但你说了竞选连任 我指的是参选 好吗？
- But you said reelection. - I meant election, okay?
这就像说i易燃的和容易燃烧的
It's like saying flammable or inflammable.
都是一样的意思 我闻到了有猫腻的味道
- It's the same thing. - I smell a fucking rat.
哦 闭嘴 我也告诉你那是什么意思
- Oh, stop it. - I'll tell you what it is, too.
那就是这整个政府班子
It's this whole administration.
我会在这整个东西下面点把火
And I'm gonna light a fire under the whole thing.
然后我们就会找出是易燃的还是容易燃烧的了
Then we'll find out whether it's flammable or inflammable.
走 小器的基佬 走了
Come on, Wilbo Faggins, let's go.
好吧 我亲爱的副总统班子在哪？
Okay, where are my beautiful veeple people?
这有一个 我需要我的副总统班子
There's one. I need my veeple
来我的办公室 请
to come into my office, please.
嘿 J老爹来了 女士们兴奋起来吧
Hey, it's J-Diddy. Ladies get giddy.
Jonah 嘿 听着 帮我解决点事 好的
- Jonah. Hey, listen, settle something for me. - Okay.
你喜欢做爱和旅游？
You like to have sex and you like to travel?
是的 女士 那么你可以滚了
- Yes, ma'am. - Then you can fuck off.
但如果你需要我的话我就在这
But I shall be right here if you need me.
就像是象征着....的大橡树... 女士
Like the mighty oak that stands for-- ma'am.
我有话要说
I have something to say.
我完全不知道你要说什么
I've literally no idea what you're gonna say.
我不会离开 总统会离开
I'm not leaving. POTUS is leaving.
他不会竞选连任了
He's not gonna run for a second term.
我会参选 哦 天哪
- I'm gonna run. - Oh, my God!
我会竞选总统! 哦 耶!
- I'm gonna run for president! - Oh, yeah!
太棒了 我完全没想到啊
- That's awesome. - I did not see that coming.
Selina Meyer 她点燃了他们 砰!
Selina Meyer, she deals 'em fire. Bam!
砰! 我们这是要上天了!
Boom! Let's go to the fucking moon!
我之前离住在我的船上已经这么近了
I was this close to living on my boat.
哦 天哪 我只 恭喜 女士
- Oh, my God. I'm just-- - Congratulations, ma'am.
能让我
Can you give me
和我的核心队伍呆一会吗？
some time with my core team?
呃 Br Br
- Um, Br-- Br- - Ed.
当然
Bre-- Ed. - of course.
我觉得我好像错过了什么
I feel as though I may have missed something.
如果你们要跟我汇报...
If you need to fill me in on that--
嘿 里面什么事？
Hey, what happened in there?
他们庆祝的是…
They're celebrating
你不在里面
because you weren't in there.
齿轮已经在转动
Gears are already turning.
我在你的头上看到了一个灯泡 叮!
- I see a lightbulb above your head. - Bing!
好了 现在听着 所以...
Okay, now listen, so...
你们不需要找其他工作了
you guys don't need to take other jobs.
你们在这 和我一起
You're here with me.
呃 我已经接受了不少职位
Uh, I've accepted a number of posts.
你刚说了不少？ 现在是四个
Did you say a number? - Currently four.
喔 你会拒掉他们的 对吧？
Wow. You're gonna cancel them, right?
哦 当然 是的 哦 是的
Oh, clearly. Yeah. Oh, yeah.
我对所有的都说了不 女士 我为您而存在
I've said no to everything, ma'am. I am here for you.
好 嘿 女士
- Good. - Hey, ma'am.
我也找了份工作
I took a job also.
我之前没说过你 Gary 我知道
- I didn't mean you, Gary. - I know.
什么工作？
What job?
我会去和Dana做生意
I'm going into business with Dana
我们会一起做D&G进口奶酪
and we're doing D&G Cheese Overseas.
奶酪？ 是进口的
- Cheese? - And it's overseas.
等一会 你选择了过期牛奶而不是我？
Wait a minute. You're choosing dead milk over me?
不 别那么说 那不是事实
No, don't say that. That's not true.
哦 你只需要告诉她你不会那么做
Well, you're just gonna have to tell her you're not gonna do that.
我不能 我不能那么对她说
I can't. I can't tell her that.
为什么不？ 你害怕她？
Why not? Are you scared of her?
是的 好吧
Yeah. - Okay.
Gary 你不能让那个女人
Gary, you cannot let this woman
控制你 好吗？
have control over you, okay?
说真的 你得为自己坚强起来
Seriously, you have got to stick up for yourself.
你得为我工作
You gotta work for me.
是的 是的 我非常害怕她
Right. Right. She scares me a lot.
很好 打电话给她 我来跟她说
All right, call her in and I'm gonna talk to her.
好吗？ 好的 嗯 知道了
- Okay? - Okay, yeah. Got it.
女士 30分钟后有科技展览
Ma'am, science fair in 30 minutes.
好吧 你去处理那个 而你去替Gary的班 好吗？
Okay, you go deal with that and you cover for Gary, okay?
你相信我能处理那个Leviathan？
You trust me with that Leviathan?
呃 女士 我把我的黑莓忘在...
Uh, ma'am, I left my BlackBerry in--
好了 现在听着 我得去这个科技展览
Okay, now listen, I got this science fair thing.
我想让我的讲话
So I want to make my speech
多一点总统味 哦
a little bit more presidential. - Yeah.
就像我是玛丽莲·梦露
Like I'm Marilyn Monroe,
就给我狠狠地体现一把 肯尼迪的味道 (二人有染)
just JFK the fuck out of me.
哦 我有主意了 你确定？
- Ooh, I got something. - You do?
没错 我有 我有想法了 棒极了
- Yeah, I do. I got something. - Fantastic.
我完全不知道发生了什么 如果
I'm just completely in the dark. If--
我去打电话给Andrew 唔嗯
I'm gonna go call Andrew. Mm-mm-mm.
呃 呃 不 不 不 完全是说钱的事 Ame
- Uh-- uh-- - No, no, no, it's all about crazy money, Ame.
他有大笔的钱
He's got the crazy money
而我足够疯狂去要这些钱
and I'm crazy enough to go get it.
只要你别夹带私活就行
As long as it's strictly business.
Andy？ 是我
Andy? It's me.
是Lee
It's Lee.
你能过来这里吗？
Can you come here?
哦 他在那
Oh, there he is.
嘿 别这么热辣 会把我所有的奶酪都融化的
Hey, quit being so hot. You're gonna melt all my cheese.
嗨 你 你好 亲爱的 嗨
- Hi, you. - Hi, sweetie. Hi.
嘿 怎么了？
Hey, what's wrong?
你的表情就像我叫你说脏话的时候一样
You look like you did when I asked you to talk dirty.
你就像 "我现在正在你身体里" 嘘 我知道 我知道
- You were just like, "I'm in you right now." - Shh. I know, I know.
停 停 我想跟你说些事
Stop, stop. I wanted to talk to you about something.
Selina会留下来
Selina's gonna stay.
好吧 呃 这件事已经定下来了
Okay. Well, that ship has sailed.
你现在正在好船Pecorino(奶酪名)上
You're on the good ship Pecorino now.
是的 我也会留下来 我想
Yeah, I'm gonna stay, too, I think.
不行 不行 好吧 听着
- No. No. - Okay, listen--
Toscano奶酪在哪？ 在D12
- Where's the Toscano? - It's at D12.
就在那边 好吗？ 她需要我
That's right over there, okay? She needs me.
就像我是她的中枢神经系统
It's like I'm her central nervous system.
亲爱的 她会找到另一个背包的小兔子 我就知道
Honey, she'll get another bag bunny, I just know it.
不 Brett 在更底下 那是Sardo奶酪 伙计
No, Brett, it's further down. That's the Sardo, buddy.
好吧 我不是背包的兔子
Okay, I'm not a bag bunny.
在那我就像是Selina的灵魂伴侣
It's like I'm Selina's soul mate over there.
好吧 我爱你这个人的全部 Gary 我知道你爱
- Okay, I love the stinking shit out of you, Gary. - I know you do.
她不爱你 好吗？ 她不在乎
She doesn't love you, okay? She doesn't care.
她真的在乎 你就是个给她工作的人
- She does care. - You're just a guy that does a job for her.
那不是事实 谁对你而言更重要？
- That's not true. - Who's more important to you?
我还是她？ 好吧 那个选择 没法
- Me or her? - Okay, that choice, there's no way--
我们有什么是有黑松露的？
Do we have any with black truffle?
那是F15 好吗？
That's F15. Okay? F15.
听着 你让我在你和她之间选择 这是不可能的
Listen, the choice you're giving me between you and her, that's impossible.
抱歉 没有黑松露 我说的是白松露
Sorry, not black truffle. I meant white truffle.
就在黑松露的旁边 好吗
That's next to the black truffle, okay.
你他妈什么毛病 Brett？
What the fuck is wrong with you, Brett?
这不是个大地方 好吗？ 这不是个大地方
This is not a big place, is it? It's not a big place.
我很抱歉 你们需要一些空间吗？
I'm sorry. Would you guys like some space?
当然! 不! 呆在那别动
- Yeah! - No! Stay right where you are.
好吧 听着 她想跟你谈谈
Okay, listen, she wants to talk to you.
她想对你解释这个 好
She wants to explain this to you. - Fine.
好吗？ 拜托？ 我会去
- Okay? Please? - I'll go.
我不害怕为你而战 Gary 这就是真相
I'm not afraid to fight for you, Gary. That's the truth.
不 不 不 别 别 别 别
No, no, no. Bah, bah, bah, bah.
真的 让我们不要战斗 好吗？
Let's literally not fight, all right?
好吗？ 那是好奶酪
Okay? That's good cheese.
Amy 这真的成真了
Amy, this is really happening.
你知道 听着 别去管早些时候的我
You know, listen, just ignore that earlier me.
那个狗屁的"大草原上的小房子"
The "Little House on the Prairie" bullshit.
不 更新的我 全部精神集中在事业上
No, updated me, totally career focused
目标白宫
and shooting for the White House.
当然 我就在你身后/身旁
Of course, and I am right behind/beside you.
你 总统的办公厅主任
You, Chief of Staff to the president,
而我...主管性感和侧抱
me, chief of sexiness and spooning.
没错 但就像我说的 现在的重心
Yeah, but as I said, the focus right now
必须是...
has got to be...
嘿 Amy 我能和你谈谈吗？
Hey, Amy, can I talk to you about something?
突发的大囧事
Accidental dick move.
我写Selina在科技展览上的讲话写得太快
I had to write Selina's speech for the science fair so fast
导致我觉得我抄了我给Chung准备的谈话
that I think I plagiarized a speech that I wrote for Chung.
这是Selina的文本
So here's Selina's hard copy
而Chung的已经上传到他的YouTube上了
and Chung's is already up on his YouTube.
我遇到了个叫Juanita的年轻姑娘
I met a young woman name Juanita.
哦 就是这段 这和美国对我而言是什么无关
- Oh, here's the bit. - It's not about what America means to me.
而是我对美国来说意味着什么
It's what I mean to America.
因为没有了美国人民美国就什么都不是
Because America would be nothing without Americans.
天 你写了这段屁话？
Jesus, you wrote this shit?
是的 这就像一碗没有动词的汤
Yeah, it's like a noun-verb gumbo.
这就是个虚拟的女孩 我给了她同一个女孩
So it's the fictitious girl. I gave her the same girl.
尽管我把Juanita换成了Anita
Although I did change it from Juanita to Anita.
哦 那是个绝妙的计划
Oh, that's a brilliant plan.
你为什么不把美国换成蒙羞美国(shame+美国)？ 哦 我现在打给Mike
Why don't you change America to Shmamerica? Yeah, I'm calling Mike.
不用 我已经试过了 直接转到了他的语音信箱
No, I already tried him. It went straight to voice mail.
我遇见了这个叫Anita的年轻科学家
I met this young scientist named Anita.
我对她说... 你有充电器吗？
And I said to her... - you got a charger?
嘘 我正在观看 好吧 赢家
- Shh, I'm trying to watch. - Okay, champ.
...她说 "不是科学对我而言是什么
...and she said, "It's not what science means to me,
而是我对科学意味着什么"
it's what I mean to science."
让我们先做这个 这是个可以地图定位宠物的社交媒体网络
Let's do this one first. This is a mappable social media cloud for pets.
哦 我被那个惊艳了 全垒打
- Oh, I'm impressed with that. - Home run.
听着 我告诉你 三个词:
Listen, let me tell you something. Three words--
党团 初选 钱
caucus, primary, money.
对吧？  大干一场
Right? - Go big.
不 四个词 还是钱 对吧？
No, four words-- money again. Right?
因为那就是我们需要的 Mike 我们需要很多钱
'Cause that's what we need. Mike, we need a lot of money.
这里的是Rachel和Erica 女士
This is Rachel and Erica over here, ma'am.
哦 哇哦 这是什么？ 它是个蚂蚁公社
- Oh, wow, what is this? - It's an ant kibbutz.
好吧 我想要看看那个
Okay. I would love to look at that.
哦 我刚刚有个想法
Oh, and I just had a thought.
记得那个爱荷华煎牛排的东西？ 唔嗯
Remember that Iowa steak fry thing? - Mm-hmm.
我们得去那个 是的
We need to Go to that. - Yeah.
真的 因为那里有很多钱
Seriously, 'cause there's a lot of money there.
还有牛排 还有牛排 我爱那个
And steak. - And steak. I love it.
我知道你在想什么 副总统女士
So, I know what you're thinking, Madam Vice President.
你确定？ 哦 哦 有限的空间 对吧？
- You do? Uh-oh. - A confined space, right?
但这是个人文环境
But it's a humane environment.
哦 从上面看 他们看起来像蚂蚁
Well, from up here, they look like ants.
那是个笑话
That's a joke.
因为它们就是蚂蚁 这边请 女士
- Because they are ants. - This way, ma'am.
这是某种机器人 真的吗？ 就那样？
- This is some kind of robot. - Really? That's it?
我能走开一下吗？ 嘿 慢货Joe
- Would you excuse me? - Hey, Joe fucking Slow.
你有想到过要接电话吗？
You ever think about answering your phone?
冷静 我弄丢了我的充电器 你有吗？
Chill out. I lost my charger. You got one?
你在科技展览上 随便一个孩子就能给你做一个充电器
You're at a science fair. One of these kids could build you a charger.
怎么了？ Ben一整天都在试图联络副总统
- What's the problem? - Ben's been trying to get in touch with the veep all day.
好吧 呃 她很忙
All right, well, she's busy.
抱歉 Todd 很快
Sorry there, Todd. Just real quick.
哦 国家事务
Oh. - Matters of state.
先生 没错 副总统在这 是Ben
Sir, yes, I have the vice president for you. It's Ben.
给她点空间 你好 Ben 怎么样？
- Give her a little space. - Hi, Ben. How's it going?
Furlong在城里到处说
Furlong has been spraying all over town
你认为总统会退出
that you think POTUS is gonna quit.
什么？ 我没对那个暴躁的蠢货说过任何事
What? I didn't say anything to that crusty ass clown.
我大概搞混了几个词 但是...
I might have mixed up a couple words, but...
好吧 现在总统没法说他不会为连任竞选
Well, now POTUS can't say that he won't be running for reelection
因为那会让他看起来像是被迫出局的
because it'll look like he's being pushed out.
所以现在我们懦弱的
So now our spineless,
反复无常的蠢货会留下来
flip-floppy fuckbag is staying.
哦 去 一切正常吗？
- Oh, boy. - Is everything okay?
我得在我点燃这里的某个书呆子之前出去
I've got to get out of here before I set fire to one of these nerds.
好吧 好吧 走 那是我的手机
- Okay, okay, let's go. - That's my phone.
谢谢 谢谢 副总统女士
Thank you. Thank you. - Madam Vice President.
不 我们很抱歉 她真的很喜欢它
- No. - We're so sorry. She really likes it,
但不幸的是她没有时间了 伙计们
but unfortunately she's out of time, you guys.
但这里的这个男人会代替她
But this man right here is gonna take over for her.
别搞砸这个了 这会是场即将发生的公关噩梦
Don't fuck this up. This is a public relations nightmare waiting to happen.
什么事都答应他们 谢谢 孩子们
Promise them everything. Thank you, kids.
女士 你...
Ma'am, are you--
我想你会喜欢这里
I thought you'd like this spot.
现在特区秘密会面的必来之地
DC's current go-to place for these off-the-record meets.
好选择 就像我们过去常在部队里说"雷达侦测不到"
Good choice. Under the radar as we used to say in the military.
嗯 我想其他人也会这么说
Yeah, I think other people say that, too.
这和对真相的忠诚有关
It's about loyalty to the truth.
以及对美国人民的忠诚
And to the American people.
Furlong和Doyle将枪口指向了总统
Furlong and Doyle have turned their guns on the president.
这是最糟糕的一种友军炮火
That's the worst kind of friendly fire.
就是不友好的那种
The unfriendly kind.
是的 哦 Danny 我只是想让你知道
Yeah, oh, Danny, I just want to let you know,
你其中一件轶事可能意外地
one of your anecdotes may have accidentally
被我写进了副总统的讲话
made its way into a veep speech via me.
如果你能让这件事过去 我会很感激
And I'd really appreciate it if you could let this one slide.
Selina是个剽窃者？ 太完美了
Selina's a plagiarist? That's perfect.
你刚给了我一颗银子弹(杀暗黑生物的绝招)
You just handed me a silver bullet.
而如你所知 我是个好枪手
And as you know, I'm a good shot.
尽管 我大概不会叫她撒谎者
I might back away, though, from calling her a liar.
毕竟 你没有真的碰到过 一个叫Juanita并说过那些话的人
After all, you didn't really meet anyone named Juanita who said that.
不 我 有 就像我记得的那样 是这样的...
No, I did. As I recall, it went something like...
Ching先生 我来美国工作 (Chung模仿的是华人口音 而Juanita是拉丁裔名)
Mr. Ching, I come to America to work.
我把钱寄回去 但这里的生活对我来说很艰苦
I send money home, but life here is so hard for me.
我不知道你还会配音
I didn't know you did voices.
Sue 过来
Sue, come here.
Dan在哪？ 他出去了
- Where's Dan? - He stepped out.
Um, ahem.
总统决定他要留下来
POTUS has decided that he is staying,
他到底还是要寻求连任
and he is going to seek reelection after all.
他当然想留下来
Of course he wants to stay.
你能不能不...
Could you just not...
他要连任
So he's running for a second term,
就是说我不会为首任任期竞选
which means I won't be running for a first term.
那么我没有任何理由留下来 我会离开
So there's no point in my staying. I'm just gonna leave.
他又改主意了？ 是的
- So he changed his mind again? - Yeah.
天 他的脑袋里面绝对就像Escher的画 (以"迷惑的图画"出名)
Jesus, the inside of his head must be like an Escher drawing.
女士 Andrew来见您了
Ma'am, Andrew is here to see you.
哦 好 更多的伤害和失望
Oh, good, more hurt and disappointment.
有另外一件事
There is one other thing that--
我很抱歉让您失望
and I'm so sorry to let you down,
但是我会留在Selina那里
but I'm gonna stay with Selina.
你觉得你能决定
You think you get to decide
我是不是要雇用你？
on whether or not I hire you?
外面有大把的Dan Dan
There are plenty of Dans out there, Dan.
看看周围
Look around.
抱歉 孩子
Sorry, kid.
嘿 别叫我孩子 好吗？
Hey, don't call me kid, okay?
我是说 第一 你不是Jimmy Cagney (银幕硬汉) 好吗？
I mean, A: you're not Jimmy Cagney, all right?
第二 我们基本上他妈的同龄
And B: we're practically the same fucking age.
那么知道我比你取得了多得多的成就你肯定很伤心
Then it must really hurt to know how much more I've achieved in life.
满是功勋的老兵 未来的总统
Decorated veteran. President-in-waiting.
哦 好吧 你看到这个了吗？ 看到这里的这个了吗？
Oh, okay. Do you see this? See this right here?
你知道这个是什么吗？ 这是我在世界上最大的大提琴上演奏"操你丫"
You know what this is? This is me playing "Fuck You" on the world's biggest cello.
哦 我想某个人刚刚自杀性的毁灭了他自己的未来
Oh, I think someone just suicide bombed their own future.
天 你知道 如果你每次提及 那场该死的战争的时候就给我一美元的话
God, you know, if I had a dollar for every time you mentioned that goddamn war,
我的钱足够买个坦克 然后把你他妈的大肥头给轰下来
I would buy a tank and I would blow your fat fucking head off.
喔 好吧 抱歉 Dan
Wow. Well, I'm sorry, Dan.
我讨厌让人失望 但后会有期
I hate to leave a man down, but I'll see you around.
Danny. Danny, hey.
去你的你在玩我？
Are you fucking kidding me?
你让我过来 却空手而归？
You brought me over here for nothing?
你现在真的要这么对我说话？
Are you really talking to me like this right now?
我有很多事要做 我现在情况不好
I have Shit to do. - I am in a bad way.
诚实地说 那太出格了
Honestly, it's so out of line.
那太出格了 是的
- It's so out of line. - It is.
你被特区的每个人搞得一团糟
You get fucked by everybody in DC--
你的朋友 敌人
your friends, your enemies,
同事 他妈的家人
your colleagues, your fucking family.
那就是华盛顿特区
That's Washington, DC, for you.
DC 王八蛋区
DC-- District of Cunts.
女士 你记得Sally T.J.和 Paul
Ma'am, you remember Sally, T.J., and Paul.
这是我的书呆子小队 是善意的说法
This is my nerd herd. And I mean that affectionately.
Jonah 这是管制区
Jonah, this is a restricted area.
我们就像51区一样 只是管制更严格 (传说中关押外星人的区域)
We're like Area 51 except more restricted.
Jonah 你能过来一下吗？ 是的
- Jonah, can you come here just for a second? - Yeah.
你能告诉我现在是怎么回事吗？
Do you want to fill me in as to what's going on right now?
是的 女士 您突然从科技展览退场
Yes, ma'am. Your abrupt exit from the science fair.
Mike需要在公关上弥补一下 所以你得给这些家伙一个白宫西翼游
Mike needed a PR fix, so you have to give these guys a West Wing tour.
什么？ 呃 女士
- What? - Uh, ma'am.
这得停下来
This has got to stop.
你得明白总统正在路上
You should be aware that the president is on his way.
嘿 我们为什么不在这些椅子上坐一会？
Hey, why don't we go sit on these chairs for a second?
你说什么？ 总统要过来？
What did you say? The president is coming here?
是的 为什么? 他从来不过来
Yes. - Why? he never comes here.
我不知道 从信息的角度来说 我没得到消息
I don't know. Information-wise, I am becalmed.
总统要来这？
The president is coming here?
Gary Dana刚过了安检 这里一片混乱
Gary, Dana just cleared security. This is anarchy.
嘿 女士 现在不是和Dana谈话的好时机吧？
Hey, ma'am, is now a bad time to talk to Dana?
没错! 好的 让我处理好那个
- Yeah! - Okay, let me just go fix that.
我去处理好那个
I'll fix that.
嘿 嘿 Gary 我要嫁的人
- Hey. Hey. - Gary who I'm gonna marry.
未婚妻来了 哦 哦!
Fiance in the house. Ooh, ooh!
这不是个好时机 宝贝
This is not a good time, baby.
我带了Pecorino Duo Grande奶酪样品
I brought the Pecorino Duo Grande sampler.
磨细了的 好吧 我把这个给她
- Shaved and grated. - Okay, I'll just give this to her.
但是为什么？ 哦 天 是Selina吗？
But why? Oh, my God, is it Selina?
对吗？ 她不喜欢我 是那样吧？
Right? She doesn't like me, is that it?
她喜欢你 那是什么?
She loves you. - then What is it?
Shh, shh.
总统要过来 C507哦 天哪!
- POTUS is coming. - Oh, my God!
这会有很多保安 而他不希望周围有很多人
There's a lot of security and he doesn't like a lot of people around.
应该把这个篮子给他 对吧？ 我们让他发个推
He should get the basket. Right? We'll get him to tweet about it.
会是超棒的宣传 你知道我是对的
It'll be great publicity. You know I'm right.
他要和我拆伙么？
Is he gonna drop me from the ticket?
那就是现在的情况？ 他大动肝火 我不知道
- Is that what's going on? He's gone postal. - I have no idea.
女士 什么？
- Ma'am. - What?
你得冷静下来(饮料名)
You've got to mello yellow.
别告诉我不要惊慌
Don't tell me not to panic.
我知道怎么崩溃 好吗？
I know how to freak out, okay?
所有人都他妈闭上嘴
Everybody can just shut the shit up.
我得想想 好吧
I got to think. - Okay.
我们知道她怎么样 Andrew 别跟我说话
- We know what she's like. - Andrew, don't talk to me.
女士 我要不要让Jonah把那些孩子...
Ma'am, should I get Jonah to get the kids--
我会让Jonah把那些孩子带出去
I'll get Jonah to get the kids out.
Jonah 你为什么不把孩子带到我的办公室？
Jonah, why don't you put the kids in my office?
总统要过来？ Mike.
Mike. Mike. - is The President coming?
Mike! Mike! Mike!  女士 我来了
Mike! Mike! Mike! Mike! Mike! Mike! - Ma'am, I'm coming.
我来了 我来了 过来这里
- I'm here. I'm here. - Come here.
我们得做个声明 好的
We got to make a statement. - Okay.
因为我认为总统要过来把我踢出去
Because I think POTUS is coming here to kick me off the ticket.
我得在他踢掉我之前作出声明说我要离开
And I've got to make a statement saying I'm leaving the ticket
你知道我得在我们遭黑手之前跳出来
before he drops me from it. I've got to jump before we get stabbed in the back.
好吧 Danny Chung做了个声明 什么?
Danny Chung is making an announcement. - What?
我很自豪曾在部队服役
I was proud to serve in the military.
我很自豪作为州长为民众服务
I'm proud to serve as a governor.
今天我设立了探索委员会
Today I've set up an exploratory committee
来调查未来几年内... 好吧
to Look into whether in a couple of years... - Okay.
我是否可能在更高层的位置上发挥作用
...I might be of use serving at an even higher level.
她让你开心吗？ 因为我让你开心
Does she make you happy? Because I make you happy.
你当然让我开心 宝贝 那整个...
Of course you make me happy, baby.
女士 我们得请你离开 这是怎么回事？
- Ma'am, we're gonna have to ask you to leave. - What is this?
哦 天哪 怎么了？
Oh, my God. What's going on?
我们回去再说
We are gonna talk about this when we get home.
你是我的钻石 我是钻石原石
- You are my diamond. - I am a diamond in the rough.
我知道你是钻石 把你的手拿开
- I know you're a diamond. - Get your hands off me.
我知道我要做什么
I know what I'm gonna do.
我要作为Chung的对手参选
I'm gonna run against Chung.
好吗？ 我要和总统散伙 Okay？
Okay? I'm gonna take myself off the ticket.
我要和Chung还有总统竞争
I'll run against Chung and I'll run against POTUS.
这会是场政治大屠杀
It'll be like a political massacre.
别惊慌 您得过过脑子
Quit freaking out. You need to get your head together.
你什么意思？ 我我已经下决心了 总统随时都会到…
What do you mean? The president's gonna be here any second.
瞧 瞧 瞧 瞧
Lookie, lookie, lookie, lookie.
这是给您的 什么?
this is for you. - What?
这就像个Pecorina和平献礼
It's like a Pecorino peace offering.
你他妈到底在干什么？
What the crippling fuck is going on with you?
我摆脱Dana了 你得出去
- I got rid of Dana. - You've got to get out of here.
出去 总统过来了!
- Get out of here. - I have POTUS incoming!
总统过来了! 做个声明 Mike
- I have POTUS incoming! - Make a statement, Mike.
关于什么？ 关于什么？ 所有的
about What? about What? - everything.
你能想到的所有可能的声明
All possible statements that you can even think of.
好吧 我会想出点东西的 我会想出来的
Okay, I'll come up with something.
让我们去和总统问好 别当我是疯子一样对我说话
- Let's go say hi to POTUS. - Don't talk to me like I'm a crazy person.
那不是我的本意 说出来的时候变得奇怪了
I didn't mean to. It came out weird.
空出地方来 你 总统要经过 空出地方来
Make a hole, yo. POTUS coming through. Make a hole.
你不是总统
You're not the president.
不 但是你也不是Justin Bieber对吧 失败者？
No, but you're not Justin Bieber either, are you, sport?
女士 总统在这
Ma'am. POTUS is here.
哪里
Where?
他被缩小了吗？
Has he been miniaturized?
他就在那个房间里
He's right in that room.
你介意让他进你的办公室吗？
Would you care to join him in your office?
Uh...
我要被开掉了吗？ 没有 没有 没有
- Am I about to get whacked? - No, no, no.
不 很高兴再次见到您 保重
No, it's good to see you again. Take care.
你的上司要见你 别让他等
Your boss wants to see you. Don't keep him waiting.
这里发生了什么？
What's going on here?
是让绝望的人来工作的日子？
Is it Bring a Disparate Person to Work Day?
呃 Selina正要被总统子弹爆头
Uh, Selina is about to get a Potal bullet through the head
而你们所有人就要失业然后无家可归
and you are all about to be unemployed and homeless.
但是 Amy 我不想你担忧 你可以在我家借住
But, Amy, I don't want you to worry. You can crash at my place.
我们被整死了 我们被整透了
We're so fucked. We're so fucked.
我们把特区的人都得罪了个遍
We've fucked DC over so many different ways,
现在没人会雇我们了
no one's gonna hire us now.
我他妈要怎么付我那条船的费用？
How am I gonna pay for my fucking boat?
别再说他妈的船了 Mike
Enough about the fucking boat, Mike.
找只信号枪 塞到你口里 然后把头爆了
Take a flare gun, put it in your mouth, and blow your head off.
听听你们自己 你们这些人都是怪物
Listen to yourselves. You people are monsters.
Ed 你现在真的很需要停止这个
Ed, you really need to can it right now.
别评价这个办公室 好吗？
Do not comment on this office, okay?
嘿 Sue 别那么对我说话 好吗？
Hey, Sue, don't talk to me that way, okay?
你是副总统的秘书
You're the secretary to the vice president.
那就像Garfunkel(歌手)的巡回乐队管理员 好吗？
That's like being Garfunkel's roadie, okay?
所以这是Selina的队伍在行动啊
So this is Selina's team in action.
这说明了很多 同感
that explains a lot to me. - Likewise.
是的 哦 他们实际上比我的队伍好
Yeah, well, they're actually better than my team.
我的队伍单纯的就是糟透了
My team is just fucking horrible.
女士？
Ma'am?
Hi.
我想我知道您要说什么 但是我不想当乌鸦嘴
I think I know what you're gonna say, but I don't wanna jinx it.
总统不会
POTUS is not
为连任竞选
gonna be running for a second term.
哦 天哪! 我会参选
- Oh, my God! - I'm gonna run.
哇哦 哇哦! 女士 告诉我实话
Whoa, whoa! Ma'am, give me the straight poop here.
那是真的吗？ 完全是真的
- Is this for real? - It's totally for real.
哦 谢谢! 谢谢 谢谢 谢谢
Oh, thank you! Thank you, thank you, thank you.
我们能公开吗？ 不行 不行 不行 不行
- Can we make it public? - No, no, no, no.
我们得等总统发表声明 好吧 好吧 好吧
We got to Wait for Potus to make a statement. - Okay. Okay. Okay.
女士 在所有我担任联络人的地方
Ma'am, of all the places that I have liaised,
我最喜欢这里
I have enjoyed liaising here the most.
好吧 伙计们 我们不想太提前
Okay, guys, we don't want to get ahead of ourselves here.
我们有很多事情要做 是的 前方是条漫长的路
- We've got a lot of work. - Yep, a long road ahead.
对吗？ 我们会一直走下去
- Right? - And we're going all the way.
作为记录 女士 我一直都相信您
And for the record, ma'am, I always believed in you.
哦 我得说我也相信自己
Well, I have to say that I believed in me, too.
当然 没错
- Of course. - Yeah.
总统 他知道形势变得很严峻
POTUS, he knew the gig was up
因为Doyle Furlong Chung...
because Doyle, Furlong, Chung
全部让党内反对他
all turned the party against him.
我是说 那就是 安息吧总统
I mean, it was just, you know, RIP-OTUS.
就是完全没希望了
Just complete sinking shit.
不 他得离开 我们会一起创造历史
No, he had to go. Together we are going to make history.
我们会去白宫 女士
We're going to the White House, ma'am.
砰 砰 完成
Boom, boom, pow.
哦 是的 是的 喔
Oh, yeah. Yeah. Wow.
我的大脑为您服务 女士
My brain is at your service, ma'am.
等着瞧吧 女士 我太激动了
- We'll see. - Ma'am, I am so psyched.
科技展览的讲话是抄了Chung的
And the science fair speech was plagiarized from Chung.
只是希望提前让您知道
Just wanted you to know that up front.
什么? 什么? 什么? 什么? 是的
What? What? What? What? - Yep.
你在开玩笑 没有
- You're kidding. - No.
那么开始了 是的 让人蛋疼的一击
- And so it begins. - Yeah, with a kick to the tits.
那么 Dan 你自己搞出来的烂摊子你自己收拾
So, Dan, you're gonna have to clean up your own shitty diaper.
明白吗？ 没问题
- Got it? - Not a problem.
哦 等等 你知道吗？ 我们得谈谈竞选活动了 不是吗？
You know what? We got to talk about the campaign, don't we?
好的 我就在你背后支持你 好 棒极了
- Okay. I'm right behind you. - Okay, great.
Gary 打电话给Dana 她打过来了90次
Gary, call Dana. She's called 90 times.
去 跟她谈 然后让她安静
- Shit. - Talk to her, then sedate her.
女士 总统已经离开这栋大楼了
Ma'am, the president has left the building.
他妈的谁关心？
Who gives a flying fuck?
还没有 抱歉 我很抱歉 但我控制不住
- Not yet. - Sorry. I'm sorry, but I couldn't help it.
女士 西翼
Ma'am, West Wing.
这是你的错 不 不
- This is your fault. - No, no.
我到得不够早 以至于我没法切除这个肿瘤
I didn't arrive soon enough to be able to cut out the cancer.
哦 不 我认为你是带着充满肿瘤的卵袋来的
Oh, no, I think you arrived with a man bag filled with tumors.
那是总统的问题
That was POTUS's problem.
因为他依靠着那两个人
Because he relied on those two guys.
一个是精疲力尽的失败者 另一个是装瞎的机器人
One a burnt-out loser, the other a conniving robot.
疯狂 糟糕的组合 没错
- Crazy. - Bad combo, yeah.
哦 你们好 孩子们 请进
- Oh, hello, kids. - Come on in.
哦 天 你们一直都在这？
Oh, my God, have you been here this whole time?
M&M (巧克力糖) 给科学家们
M&Ms for the scientists.
跟我一起来 因为我有个好主意
So come with me 'cause I've got an idea.
我大概会带你们逛逛西翼
I might show you around the West Wing.
啊! 真的？
- Ahh! - Would you?
你们喜欢政府吗？ 是的
do you Like government? - Yes.
你们喜欢政治吗？ 是的
And do you Like politics? - Yeah.
哦 好 因为政治就是和人有关 你们不这么认为吗？
Oh, good. Because politics is about people, don't you think?
没错 它是 当你思考的时候
Yeah. - It is when you think about it.
因为没有人 就不可能有政治
'Cause without people, you can't have politics.
看这多热闹？
See how crowded this is?
我是说 这很容易引起幽闭恐怖症
I mean, it's very claustrophobic.
我想总统应该只让她的人员在这
I think that the president should only have her staff here.
或者他的员工 你知道 他们的
Or his staff. You know, their staff.
我是说 我从没见过 就像我们刚刚经过的那个
I mean, I've never seen-- like that one we just passed,
我不知道那是谁
I don't know who that person is.
在我的生命中我就没见过那个人
I've never seen that person in my life.
在这不知道干嘛
No business being here.
Selina没有抄袭Danny Chung的讲话
Selina did not plagiarize Danny Chung's speech.
Mike已经告诉你那个了
Mike's already told you that.
不 我没有抄袭Mike
No, I am not plagiarizing Mike.
我知道这很无聊 但是 嘿 我就是很无聊
I know it's boring, but, hey, I'm boring.
那些窗帘...要拆掉
Those curtains there are going.
天哪 真是丑
Wow, those are hideous.
我们还是在一起的 对吧？ Ed 我没时间
- We're still together, right? - Ed, I haven't got time.
我们的时间还是指一般意义上的时间？
Time for us or do you mean time as a general concept?
你好 Terry 抱歉我错过了你的电话
Hi, Terry. I am sorry I missed your call.
你好 Dana 嘿 嘿 听着
Hi, Dana. Hey. Hey, listen.
我只是想说
I just wanted to say that--
好吧 好吧 如果你有什么要说 你先
Okay. Okay. If you've got something to say, you go first.
当她说"哦 天 哦 天"的时候 你妈妈有在抄袭圣经吗？
Was your mom plagiarizing the Bible when she said, "Oh, God, oh, God"?
总统的椅子
The president's chair is a couple inches higher
比总统办公室的其他椅子都要高几英寸
than the rest of the chairs in the Oval Office.
我以前常常想 "哦 天 那太可笑了"
And I used to think, "Oh, my God, that's so ridiculous."
但现在我觉得这很有意义
But now I think it makes sense
因为我认为这是个不错的心理暗示
because I think it's a good psychological trick.
是的 那就是我... 你还没说完？ 继续
Yeah, that's what I-- you're not finished? Go ahead.
哦 她喜欢那些奶酪
Oh, she loved the cheese.
很喜欢
Loved it.
当我长大的时候 我想像您一样成为副总统
When I grow up, I want to be vice president just like you.
哦 不 你不会 你会想成为总统的
Oh, no, you don't. You want to be president.